Hi! I dropped by the library.
Hi! 我到图书馆去了一下.
They have a bunch of new CDs
他们那儿有不少新CD,
Are you OK?
你没事吧?
Your daughter has it in for me.
你的女儿存心要跟我过不去.
Oh, now she's my daughter.
Oh,现在她成了我的女儿了,
That's not a good sign. Did you have a fight?
这可不是个好兆头. 你们吵架了?
-Oh yes.  -What about?
-Oh yes.  -关于什么呢?
The cross-country trip.
横跨全国的旅行
Is she still going on about that?
她还在纠缠这件事吗?
I thought she would have given up on it by now.
我还以为她巳经不抱希望了呢.
Her tactic is to keep asking why.
她对付我的办法就是不停地问为什么.
I tell her all the reasons and I cannot talk her out of it.
我把道理全都告诉她了,可就是说服不了她.
When she asks why, you should say what I say.
她问为什么的时候, 你就应该学我的样子来回答.
Which is?
怎么回答?
"Because I said so."
"因为这是我说的."
That might have worked a few years ago.
这话几年以前也许还有用,
It won't work now.
现在不会奏效了.
Maybe. Do you want me to talk to her?
也许吧. 你想要我跟她谈谈吗?
No. I need to face up to this one myself.
不. 这个问题我必须自己来面对.
Don't worry, honey.
你不用担心,亲爱的.
She doesn't know it sometimes,
虽然她有时候意识不到,
but she does love you and look up to you.
但其实她是很爱你和崇拜你的.
I thought adolescent girls were supposed to act up with their mothers.
我还以为青春期的女孩一般只对妈妈发脾气呢.
Excuse me? Have we forgotten ages 12 and 13?
你说什么? 你难道忘了她十二三岁的时候了?
two solid years of tears and door-slamming?
整整两年啊,她老对着我哭啊, 摔门
And, as I recall, you could do no wrong.
还有呢,我还记得,(那时候)你做什么都是对的.
No, no, I have paid my dues, Good luck. Salsa!
No, no, 我已经尽过职了. 祝你好运. Salsa!